welcome to our advanced course on game
欢迎来到我们的游戏高级课程
theory this course covers the topics of
理论上，本课程涵盖以下主题
social choice mechanism design and
社会选择机制设计与
auctions and essentially it asks the
拍卖，本质上它要求
question if I know that agents are going
问我是否知道代理商要去
to behave game theoretically how can I
从理论上表现游戏我该如何
design interactions for them that lead
为他们设计互动
to good social outcomes the first topic
获得良好的社会成果的第一个主题
we're going to think about is called
我们要考虑的称为
social choice and here leaving aside the
社会选择，这里抛开
question of strategic behavior we asked
我们问的战略行为问题
about how to aggregate different
关于如何汇总不同
people's preferences together in a
人们的喜好在一起
sensible way I'm Kevin Layton Brown I'm
我是明智的方式，我是Kevin Layton Brown，我是
from the University of British Columbia
来自不列颠哥伦比亚大学
my co instructors who you'll meet in
我将与您见面的共同指导者
subsequent videos are Matt Jackson and
随后的视频是Matt Jackson和
Yoav shoham from Stanford University
斯坦福大学的Yoav Shoham
let's get started so social choice is
让我们开始吧，所以社会选择是
essentially the problem of voting and
本质上是投票和
the first thing that you might think is
您可能会想到的第一件事是
that voting seems like an incredibly
投票似乎令人难以置信
simple thing to study how hard can it be
研究它有多难的简单事情
to study something that after all
毕竟学习一些东西
involves just filling in one of the
涉及只是填写其中之一
boxes out of some small set of different
一小盒不同的盒子
candidates well I want to argue that
候选人很好我想说
that voting actually is tricky enough
投票实际上很棘手
that we want to have a mathematical
我们想要数学
theory of it here's an example in the
理论，这是一个例子
year 2000 the US presidential election
2000年美国总统大选
came down to who won Florida and it was
归结于谁赢得了佛罗里达，那是
incredibly close after complicated
复杂之后难以置信的关闭
recounts and an appeal to the Supreme
重述并向最高​​法院上诉
Court George Bush turned out to be the
乔治·布什法院原来是
winner by 537 votes
537票冠军
however Ralph Nader a third party
但是拉尔夫·纳德（Ralph Nader）是第三方
candidate with a pretty limited amount
数量有限的候选人
of support got 97 thousand votes in
的支持者中有9.7万票
surveys that were taken after the
在
election it turned out that about twice
选举结果表明，大约两次
as many Nader voters would have chosen
正如许多纳德选民所选择的
Al Gore instead of George Bush if Nader
如果纳德（Alder），则用戈尔（Al Gore）代替乔治·布什（George Bush）
hadn't been a candidate in the election
还没参加选举
now leaving the site whatever
现在无论离开网站
preferences we might have about who
我们可能对谁有偏好
should be President of the United States
应该是美国总统
this seems like a bad outcome because it
这似乎是一个不好的结果，因为它
seems like more people overall preferred
似乎总体上有更多人偏爱
Gore
戈尔
bush in Florida and nevertheless Bush
布什在佛罗里达州，但布什
was the winner so it seems like we
是赢家，所以好像我们
didn't do a very good job in this
在这方面做得不好
election about taking everybody's
选择每个人的选举
preferences into account and selecting
偏好设置并选择
the right winner
正确的赢家
indeed recently there have been popular
确实最近有流行
movements around the world demanding new
要求新的世界运动
voting systems here I'm showing protests
我在这里投票制度示威
in London and in Ottawa by British and
在伦敦和渥太华由英国人和
Canadian citizens who think that they
认为自己的加拿大公民
should have new voting systems that do a
应该有新的投票系统
better job of taking their whole
做好全部工作
preferences into account in this week of
本周的偏好设置
the course we're going to ask whether
当然，我们要问是否
it's really true that there are other
确实有其他
voting systems that are better and what
更好的投票系统以及什么
better actually means so we're gonna
更好的是意味着我们要
start by looking at different voting
首先看不同的投票
schemes seeing how they work we're gonna
计划，看看他们如何工作，我们要
see that each of these voting schemes is
看到每个投票方案是
sometimes able to give rise to kind of
有时能够引起
paradoxical outcomes where it seems like
看起来很矛盾的结果
something wrong can sometimes happen and
有时可能会发生错误，
we're gonna culminate in a famous proof
我们将以著名的证明达到高潮
that shows that in a really formal
这表明在一个真正正式的
mathematical sense it just isn't
从数学意义上讲不是
possible to avoid these kinds of
可能避免这种情况
failures so thanks for joining our
失败，所以感谢您加入我们
course and look forward to having you
当然，期待有你
for the videos to come
让视频来